# Hello, I'm Aaron Campbell

#### BIO

I am a media producer, editor, and coordinator with four years of experience in digital marketing. My academic background and professional training are rooted in the digital arts and sciences making me proficient in operating design and web programs such as Adobe Premiere Pro and WordPress. I am motivated by opportunities that will allow me to work creatively.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

MARCH 2020 - AUGUST 2021

#### Ecwid E-commerce, Denver, CO - Partner Marketing Coordinator

- Coordinated the digital media strategy and developed content for landing pages, search and display ads, and promotional videos.
- Researched market verticals in the B2B SaaS industry and used account-based marketing to generate demand and sales leads.
- Implemented and customized a Partner Resource Management (PRM) system, built on WordPress, to provide partners with sales collateral and program resources.
- Produced and led training webinars and created instructional documents to onboard 500+ partner organizations to the PRM system.

OCTOBER 2017 - JANUARY 2020

### **Rebate Bus, Madison, WI** - *Marketing Manager*

- Developed written, graphic, and video content for the website, email campaigns, social media, pitch decks, webinars, service proposals, and product demonstrations.
- Designed the user experience and launched websites using WordPress and Shopify content management systems.
- Created and executed sales toolkits for the customer resource management (CRM) system to track sales activities and automate content marketing campaigns.
- Produced and distributed printed sales materials for exhibiting and attending industry events.

#### **EDUCATION**

SEPTEMBER 2013 - MAY 2017

## University of Wisconsin, Madison, WI - Bachelors of Science

Completed a major in *Economics* and earned a certificate in *Digital* Studies from coursework in art, media, communications, and web design, growing my proficiency in using the Adobe Creative Suite.

OCTOBER 2021

Boulder Digital Arts, Boulder, CO – Video Production Certificate Boulder Digital Arts, Boulder, CO – Adobe Premiere Pro Video Editing Certificate